Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
My father was a sailor.
My only memories of him are.
His white uniform and his love for his family.
One day. he went and was never returned.
His presence.
instantly disappeared.
Why is it turned out like this?
How could this happened?
Mother was too grieved over his departure.
Which soon. she left me too. I was alone by then.
Love was not for someone like me
I grew without love
There were many sexual abuse case on the media
Because of that. I have to survive.
Wonderful Nightmare
Don't trust anyone too much.
Although. social relation is important.
Recently. the increase on homicide and sexual abuse rate.
This rumour had widely spread.
And had concerned many people.
About those incidents.
Turn the radio off.
Those animals have to be castrated.
What's with prosecutors nowadays?
Justice is rare indeed.
Yes. Director. It's me.
All right.
Yes. I understand.
Turn back. to the Prosecutor's Office.
Lawyer Lee.
Lawyer Lee Yi Ahn.
Is it true that the construction's company also responsible on this case?
As seen on the victim.
It's clear.
This has nothing to do with Group.
It's personal matter.
Don't relate this with another case.
Is this a defense for Chairman Park?
A confession from a female student of a sexual abuse doesn't mean anything?
Do you think it's for the best?
I have yet into any conclusion.
So. I hope you all not to make your own stories.
- Good bye.
- Tell us the truth now.
Lawyers should've give clear informations.
Ms. Ji Min's mother. this is...
a difficult time for you.
This damned guy.
Does not really cares.
A$*#@#!
Right. he's an a$*#@#.
But. you should know.
Hu Ji Group is one of ten most influential groups.
Cha Ji Hoon's presence.
As soon as he started his work in another country.
No one's going remember about this.
But. how can Miss Ji Min.
if she'd ever actually graduate from the university.
is able to find a marriage partner if it's this way?
But. the problem is...
The news on Miss Ji Min's identity had widely spread online.
It's no wonder that people had called her things.
It's clearly isn't a rape case.
You've never know about raising a child.
So you'll never know about the pain.
NEVER!
Mom. the lawyer's right.
Her words are all true. Let's stop this.
We'll stop this.
As long as you can give us compensation money.
Clever girl.
All right. I'll clear things up.
Wah. a sky-high priced lawyer.
...is really worth it. You're cool indeed.
Lee Yi Ahn.
You've come. Seonbae.
I never thought I could ever see you again.
It looks like you still handle cases.
I still can't believe it. seeing you again.
It's because I'm busy.
See you later.
If you keep going on like this.
You'll run into troubles.
Why? Why can't I?
Seonbae too. was once taken away public's money.
I have to do this too. to survive.
Aren't we all the same?
Do you remember.
when we were still in training?
There were hardships. sacrifices.
Some even tried to suicide.
What's with you Seonbae?
You're too emotional.
Being too emotional's the reason you're unimproved.
You're too childish. Seonbae.
Last week. a person who went into the blind date.
can find his true love. finally.
Not another love story.
Is it because you're not capable of it?
Isn't there any other interesting news?
Interesting? What's the matter with you?
To love is the most important thing that can happen to someone.
My 100th record.
You really are too much.
Lawyer Lee. there's a call from Chairman Park.
Let's begin this.
You've cleared my son's case today.
Had caused you some troubles.
No. it's been in my work for this.
Thank you for your concern. sir.
You're too humble. Shouldn't you be celebrating a little. for yourself?
Why did you choose this place?
It might've look a little ugly because it's an unfamiliar area.
But. it's a private area.
So. I don't have to be worried of being seen.
Of my meeting with you here.
There's something I wish you to do.
Please. elaborate the details.
It was originally a five-years apartment's construction schedule.
But. I wish that you'd able to put the date forward instead.
What do you think?
Can you put the date forward?
Consider it done.
I've been given this work from an U.S. branch company.
I hope that you can approve of it.
Ah. why is there not enough of street lights here?
My phone.
There's no time for me to be here.
I have to go and earn some money.
Please allow me. for this time only.
Excuse me. why am I here?
What is this?
Please tell me your name.
Lee Yi Ahn.
Date of birth.
October 23. 1976.
Please wait a minute.
It's always like this.
Why are you always act this sloppy?
It was already confirmed clearly.
Kang Soo Yeon should be taken next month. not now.
Give back the 1.3 million.
Why's it hard for you to handle even this thing?
Chairman.
What?
It looks like there's another mistake.
Lee Yian's death had been replaced.
Because of a spelling mistake. apparently.
This is what you meant by everything's fine.
Damn.
Miss Lee Yian. 76 years old.
Aigoo.
She should've lived until 2054.
So. why did you choose her?
What do we say about it to upper management?
She had until 2054. it's still years from now.
Not now.
Why are you always have to cause such trouble for me?
Then. what can we do.
To proceed Lee Yian's schedule. 76 years old.
have to switch her with the 41 years old one.
It would take a week.
It's Miss Kang Soo Yeon who should've died first.
The problem is.
She should be in a traffic accident. and died a month later.
But. because of a heart attack. she died a month earlier.
Just. delay her for a month.
Please. have a seat.
This is Heaven's Path Foundation..
Simply put. someone who had just passed away as you are now.
Is clarified before they're sent to heaven.
Passed away? Who?
Me? What are you talking about?
Don't be like this. Me?
Why do I have to die this young?
I'm still alive.
It was only a small accident.
Miss Lee.
How unreasonable. Do you know how much money was for that car?
It's not from a normal accident.
Lee Yi Ahn.
I beg of you. Save me. Please.
Please calm down and have a seat.
Calm down.
We've also agreed to change your death schedule.
This is what would've happened.
Lee Yi Ahn. an innocent person.
A special service had been prepared.
The system would bring you back on Earth.
It means I can return?
Thank you very much.
But. to gain that system.
Thank you.
You have to help us.
What do I have to do?
There's a mistake on time format.
Because of our mistake. you had come earlier here.
Would Miss Lee like to be alive during the rest of this month?
Do you mean my life won't end until next month?
Correct.
It's a mistook summon.
You will return to your old life.
But. how?
I'll decide later.
But. this month.
Don't let this be known to anyone.
and you would live another life.
What do you think?
Isn't it in favor for both of us? Or. would you like straight to heaven?
All right. I'll do it.
Stand in the circle. please.
Hand on screen.
Concentrate.
Where's this?
This is...
What's wrong?
What is it?
Phone. my phone.
Is it the underwear thief?
Where?
Who's there?
No one's here. Maybe you're wrong.
You.
Is it me?
Do you think I'm the thief?
Who stole your underwear?
The one you wear right now is mine.
See. It's mine.
Is it because you mimic last night's film?
Don't come closer. No.
I'll throw this at you.
I'm late. anyway. I have to go.
Ah.
What is it?
The Scream. The Scream.
Do you mimic The Scream?
It's not that.
What is it if not that?
It can't be.
After I graduate school.
I'm positive about this.
I don't want to go to university.
I want to be an actress.
Who are you?
Oh. I see. You want to kick me out.
I should've known.
So. why is Ajumma here? Who are you?
Why am I here. really?
Mom.
- Why is this kid keep getting closer?
- Mom.
Don't come closer. No.
10.000 Won.
Ten thousand Won?
Hurry up. or I'll be late.
Quick.
Really...
I'm going now.
I'll be late. but I can't leave breakfast.
Come here. my boy.
- Dad
- Did you sleep well?
Why are you just standing there? Can you prepare some breakfast?
Breakfast?
You hadn't cooked any yet?
Do you think that I'm your wife?
Why are you still following those film scenes?
It'd be ugly if neighbours heard of this.
I have to hurry.
I'll have breakfast somewhere. then.
You should've cooked something for the children.
I'm going now.
Why'd you let the children eat this?
I have to hurry.
Cook some rice.
Why won't you cook something. hurry.
Who are you. actually?
Why is everyone yelling and asking for food?
How would I do this?
Help me. please.
I wake up with a husband.
And on top of it. TWO CHILDREN.
Mom.
Take this.
Yes?
1981.
It's true that I'm 34 years old. then.
Hurry up. or we'll late.
Hold on.
Good morning.
Hello. Good morning.
How are you. Ha Neul's mother?
Thank you for the red ginseng you sent me.
Did I?
Pardon?
Ha Neul's mother.
Is my name Ha Neul?
Ha Neul is Noona's name.
Why don't you know your own daughter's name?
So. that rude girl's name is Ha Neul.
Why is the ad paper's on the lift always torn up?
It's impossible for the children to have done that.
Someone saw it yesterday.
Even for money. you can't do that.
It's not me.
What?
Can't you be a little more polite?
I think. aren't we close?
How funny.
Are you asking for a fight?
Mom. let's hurry up.
Don't push me. Stop pushing.
What's gotten into her. really?
We'll be late.
Stop it.
Ha Roo.
Ha Neul's mother. are you ready for today?
Eonni. I've brought over some kimchi.
Would you like to try?
Don't. I've tried it yesterday.
It's too salty.
What did you say?
It's tasty.
Thank you.
It's the bus.
Good morning. everyone.
Slow down.
Have a nice day.
Take care. seonsaengnim.
Bye.
Where are you going?
I have something important to do.
Don't be like that.
Let's do it together again.
Let's go.
Until next time.
We've arrived on time before someone else come.
As long as we still have some left. we'd give it out.
- Thank you.
- Take care.
He's from The Philippines. but he has good manners.
Handsome. too.
Aren't you glad that I introduced him to you?
So each gets 35 Won.
Better than nothing.
True. True.
In total. we'd get 350.000 Won a month.
It'd be more than enough for premium meals in a month.
Thanks a lot.
But. why do I have to do this?
Enough with the complains.
Isn't this our side job?
Completely legal.
So. am I in this too?
Of course.
Excuse me. there's something I have to do.
Why are you like this today?
Don't run away.
Let's have a drink. then.
Okay.
We're already drinking this early in the morning.
It's pretty good.
Try some.
So tasty.
Eat it. Take the biggest one.
Tell us.
When you deliver your daughter in your house.
Yes. that one.
I did? In the house?
Really. Did I?
Why are you keep teasing us?
Is it because that you've watched too many dramas? Just tell the story.
I don't understand. I've never watched any dramas.
I don't know her. It has nothing to do with me.
Ya. did you heard what she just said?
You. really!
So ridiculous!
After you'd been married for 18 years.
There's nothing much that they can imitate from dramas. only flowers and such.
True.
18 years? It's been that long?
Impossible.
I'm now 34 years old.
I gave birth when I was a teenager?
You still can't believe it?
True. It is unbelievable.
Even us can't understand it.
What's with you? Eonnie?
Excuse me. I'm going to the toilet.
It's over there.
Eonnie? What happened?
She's so strange.
Wait. Is it...
She'll have her third child.
They're that successful.
Are you feeling better?
What is it?
You acted different than her usual self.
[The person she's now]
It's because it's not my real self.
Totally different.
Don't you want to return to your old life?
You can't return if you keep being like this. Don't be confused.
But. How can I suddenly have a husband.
And an ajumma with two children.
Also. look at what those ajummas behaviour.
I would've never able to get along with them.
They're so tacky and noisy.
Silence! If you continue it like this.
I can always return you back above.
Remember. this is a part of the test.
This isn't my real life.
Please. do enjoy your new life.
See you in a month.
This isn't a garden. is it?
Why is it a zebra here?
There's nothing worthy to wear.
This is Ha Neul's mother.
She had been married for 18 years with this man and had two children.
And lived in this shoddy place.
There's no giving up for a life of a 34 years old woman.
All right. now I know and understand.
But. I can not continue living like this.
I have my own ways.
It's all 497.500 Won.
Can you send these too. to this address?
The address is...
It's insufficient. ma'am.
Excuse me?
Why does she take it so long?
Ajumma. hurry up.
Hello.
Take your son back at the bus stop.
Ta da. look what I have here. Strawberry Milk.
Aigoo. look at this fool.
Why are you this careless? What if something bad happened?
Sorry.
Without me. what can you do?
Don't forget what you have to do.
I bought him a Strawberry Milk. too. Let's go. Ji Goo.
Let me have some of it. too.
Don't look at me like that.
We've meet several times today. haven't we?
You're right.
You hadn't bought this prawn paste?
It's so tasty. My mother make it herself.
Sorry. I don't like prawn paste.
Oh. you don't like it? Or. is it that you can't afford it?
What was it that you just said? Hold on!
It says Brada... Ah. why isn't it just says what it actually is. bra?
Who would've bought such a tacky clothes?
Shi...
Ha Neul. why are you ignoring me?
Is something happened?
Ah. Enough. Stop it.
All right. from now on I'll change myself.
Take my word as a man.
I will never disappoint you anymore.
Why you...
So annoying.
Hold on. Wait.
Something's smells good.
If you've returned home. have a seat. please.
Why is she talking weird since early in the morning?
Please have a seat. student.
You too. ajussi.
Ajussi? Is it me?
Just follow it as in the films.
Whatever. I might turned crazy from all this.
The meat looked so fresh.
Little boy. eat well. okay?
Anyway. is there no rice?
There's some potatoes in the back. you can eat those.
But. why is the sudden change?
You started cooking. too.
Not really.
ah
Really. The meat's too tough it's inedible.
I'll have something else in the fridge.
Hold on. Please sit down.
I'd like to tell you something.
I think I've been working hard.
I need some time off. too.
So. I've decided to have a holiday until next month.
Without us? Where'd it be?
For such an aged person as I. it isn't that important.
Why are you suddenly leaving like this?
How would Dad and this boy doing without you?
He's a picky eater too.
I think it's fine if it's for one day.
What is it that you think? It'll be all on me?
You're both adult. not a teenager anymore.
If you mind. why won't you have a housekeeper?
How could we do that?
To be fair. we can actually afford one.
But. you shouldn't abandon the house like that.
- So irritating.
- Calm down.
Don't leave yet. Ha Neul.
Why did you say that. out of the blue?
We should've be more patient with the first child.
Why are you like this?
Ah. What I just said was wrong. indeed.
Never mind. it might be because you're tired.
Just wash yourself up and go to sleep.
There really is no holiday. then.
Go on. sleep here.
I'm not sleepy yet.
There's something I have to tell you.
Ah. right. Next Thursday. there'll be a meeting. right?
What do you mean?
Actually. I've already told you about it that time.
Civil servants and their partners are invited.
So. you are a Civil Servant?
Yes. I am.
Is there something else you want to talk about?
Why is the card's limit so low?
What do you mean?
You'd usually use cash. anyway.
So. the amount is still 500.000.
Do I? All right.
Have the kids asleep yet?
I think they have.
Hold on. Wait.
Why?
Why are you taking your pants off?
The kids are already asleep. right?
What's with that?
You'd know what's next.
Sleep together?
Quiet. Don't yell.
You'd wake them up.
It's enough. You should stop pretending.
AH. Stop it! It hurts!
Why are you doing this?
Isn't tonight the time?
What time?
Why'd you acted like you don't know?
What do you mean?
Isn't it clear already?
It was you who fooled me!
What are you talking about?
The violation of child and woman protection law.
Rape and sexual harassment.
Actions that would be intended for sexual intercourse.
Can be sentenced and taken prisoner for at least 5 years or more.
Do you know that?
Why are you this scary. tonight?
What a shameless man!
Seduced a young girl.
And had her gave birth to two children.
Also. to live in this shoddy place.
To continue her life like this.
The most despicable guy is.
An irresponsible man.
Moreover.
Do you honestly think you can survive
relying only on your job as a civil servant?
You think it'd be that simple?
To be honest. I hate that view of the world. Especially you.
Why do you say it like that?
So. do you hate me?
This is unbelievable.
Therefore. I won't allow myself to be in a room with you.
I'd sleep on the couch.
Outside.
Pillow. Give me pillow.
Hold on!
This is unbelievable.
Why is it that I am this upset?
This is the work life. It's like that.
What...
...do you save your money for?
So I can afford a nice house. of course.
The divorce hearing would soon be confirmed.
It's for your divorce?
She likes another man.
How could she...
Take this.
Chief.
Take a look at this.
What's this?
You must've never seen this before.
It's a rejection for the construction of subway lines.
The citizens' petition.
It would be hard against the construction company.
But. there are more than 2.000 people.
This isn't the time.
You'd better do something else.
There are many other useful things.
About the Waste Budget.
- If there are many feedbacks. it'll look better.
- Enough.
Do what you can.
If it's going well. report to me.
Don't look into details that far.
Boiled corns.
Looked delicious.
A little sticky.
Don't miss this. Have some.
Eat it.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
It's nice.
Ha Neul's mother. have you found a hospital?
Right.
What hospital? What for?
Your morning sickness. It's your third child.
What third child?
You should be thankful for that.
Don't need to deny it.
I once thought that marriage could make us happy as in those fairy tales.
But. it's all unreal.
Don't be too strait-laced.
Too stiff. Too stiff.
Agreement Papers.
Ah. right. Here.
This one's mine.
This. too.
Also. this one.
I think you hadn't sign here yet.
What is it?
In this community. we lived in
the same area. So. they need our signature of approval too.
Sign here.
The construction project's reschedule.
It was originally scheduled five years after construction.
I wish to changed the date forward.
The password hadn't been changed.
Why am I this nervous?
Files.
Okay.
Is this woman Ha Neul's mother?
She's not that good-looking.
Oh right.
Let's do this.
What about the payment?
Pay in full up front. of course.
All right. let me process the transactions.
There are many new items. it seems.
Please sign here.
Let's have the bread first.
Sorry.
You're Kim Ha Neul. 12th grade. right?
Yes.
We might've just met this once.
Hello.
All right. Have a nice day.
Who's that?
A 12th grader.
I think she's cute.
It's all right. It's the same as my mom.
Is your mom like that. too?
She was. But. she's fine now.
Take your mom to my mom's hospital.
What illness is it?
Menopause. I heard she had it.
Menopause.
Can I help you. young boy?
I'd like a medicine for Menopause.
Excuse me?
It's my mom's illness.
I need a medicine for it.
Wait a minute. please.
Here you go.
But. don't tell your mom about this medicine.
Just tell her it's vitamin.
Do you get it?
Yes.
We all should've eat foods such as these in our lives.
My goodness. you surprised me. What is it?
Vitamin.
Do you want me to take it?
I can't handle bitter things.
Hurry up.
Right now?
Yes.
So bitter.
He's quite a nice child. actually.
Let's have some talk.
Hurry up. Or. the dinner would get cold.
Have a seat.
I'd prefer to stand here.
I've argued with you all day.
Ha Neul's mother had me...
Wait a minute. Don't call me Ha Neul's mother. Just call my name.
Your name?
I have a name. too.
So. don't ever call me as someone's mother ever again.
It makes me uncomfortable.
All right. Ha Neul... Ah. Soo Yeon.
I have to admit. you were still so young when you married me.
But. it was you who flirted me.
Said that you were the only one for me.
You were always well-dressed in front of me.
But. I had always said that you were stil a minor.
Hold on.
Do you know how hard it was to afford this place?
And how could you just mock it as you did?
Is that so?
Also. you said that I'm the irresponsible man type.
Do you know how much I had your life and the children's life to the better?
Hadn't I gave much efforts all this time?
Okay. Okay.
If you'd still think that I'm not good enough for you.
All right. we don't have to go on like this.
Take this.
Unbelievable.
I don't think he could ask for a divorce.
But. I should've persuade him not to.
How embarassing.
Ah. I'm hungry.
Shouldn't you be greeting me first?
Why are you keep getting upset over little things?
What?
Ha Neul's mother. What are these?
You bought new clothes.
These are so expensive. Look at the price-tags.
Even the jacket is 2.150.000 Won.
And the dress is 900.000 Won.
What's the meaning of this?
Mom. are you crazy?
It's my money. I bought these with my own money.
I bought these because I have more money.
Your money?
Get a hold of yourself.
How can you be like this?
I'm fine.
We'll talk about it later.
Who is that?
Is Mrs. Yeon Woo at home?
Yes. my wife's home.
I've already said that my Eonnie is the one who lent me.
After Lawyer Woo Yeon had a car accident.
She's now still unconscious.
Why did you stole...
Really. What do you mean by stealing stuffs?
If you think about it.
She graduated from Seoul University's Law Dept.
She should've been a top lawyer.
Please. don't mock us like that.
We still have some dignity.
Let's go.
- Let's get out of here.
- What's this?
Sit down.
We were here to aid the investigation.
Not to be accused as a criminal.
According to Act on the Performance of Duties by Police Officers. under article 2.
An investigation that is deemed as irrelevant.
have to comply to the constitution and evidence warrant of the case.
Police officers are only to help with gathering of informations.
Sufficent evidence and objectivity are mandatory.
With behaviour of officers such as you.
which is a little rough.
We will not cooperate with the investigation.
therefore. we are going home.
Is there any objection of what I just said?
No.
Tidak ada hak.
To be honest. Jang Woo Yeon was my Seonbae.
What?
Seoul University. 1999.
He was on Law studies. before he dropped off the university.
Since I had good relationships with Seonbae back then.
we often invited for various occations. dinners and such.
I'd just realised.
It was her credit card. but she gave it to me.
It's the truth. isn't it?
He's right.
All right. now you should apologise to her.
What for?
For your accusation of her.
Hurry up. before I changed my mind.
People made mistakes.
Sorry.
We've done wrong.
All right. you should be more careful from now on.
You can go home now.
I'd never knew.
that he was once on Law studies.
Dropped off university and became a civil servant.
Really..
I've never imagined to end up living like this.
My goodness.
Why'd you do that?
This is because of misunderstanding.
I'd never do such things.
You...
Are you seeing another man recently?
Another man?
Do I looked like the part?
Never mind.
Since I trusted you.
What is happening?
Why do I live my life like this?
diterjemahkan oleh :
The Moon's pretty tonight.
My goodness.
It had been only 44 hours. 14 minutes. and 28 seconds.
But. the husband had already asked for a divorce.
Stole a credit card.
and was investigated by the police.
It's not like that.
If you can only cause troubles.
Don't ever think it'll going well.
First thing is. you should reconcile with the husband.
It's because I'm too nervous if I have to talk to a man..
Up above. there are many who can replace you.
Did mom really stole those things?
How could she do that? It was only a misunderstanding of the police.
And they've admit that they were wrong.
It was really strange. right?
Mom could never do that.
Of course.
Ha Neul's mother.
All right. I'll return those.
You can wear these. actually.
What? Dad. are you crazy?
I've decided.
It's all right. You can wear these.
I'll have the money to pay for these.
Forget it. I still have things to do.
Just do as I say.
I could never allow you to dressed this tacky all this time.
You're talking about me?
Of course. Who else but you is there?
Sister. what a nice person you are.
She is such a kind person. isn't she?
Thank you.
What would had happened to us. if they begin the construction?
I have no idea.
Yes. Lawyer Kang Seo Yeon was appointed prior to her accident.
Yes. I was a friend of hers.
I called because.
I'm asking for a better compensation for the citizen.
they had agreed to the construction.
Even if her family's financial isn't that great.
but she wrote down such detailed expense.
Red ginseng's cost for security Ajussi.
My goodness.
Ah. right. I should've picked you up home.
How can you return home?
One the moms. your friend. had took me home. Also.
What's in that fool of a woman's head?
She better not be fooling off with a man somewhere!
was what she said.
Vitamins.
Another one?
Hurry. eat it.
It's really bitter.
Eat it. anyway.
Why you...
Bitter.
Why's he always give me vitamins?
Dad.
My dearest boy.
Are you tired?
Mom will cook dinner for us.
I'm home.
What are you doing?
Out of breath like that?
I've been working out.
We'll go to my office tomorrow.
Are you ready?
That's...
It's all right if you don't want to.
I'll go by myself.
First thing is. you should reconcile with the husband.
I'll go. Let's go together.
Good. I'll just take a bath first. You should prepare dinner.
Ha Neul's mother.
Is there something wrong?
No. You're very beautiful.
Why do you sound uncertain?
No. it's because you're too beautiful..
Let's go inside.
Hold on.
Hello. I'm from the urban planning department. Kim Sung Hwan.
The best and most handsome employee of the whole district.
Say hello to the Mayor.
Hello. I'm Lawyer Lee Yi Ahn.
I mean. I'm Kim Sung Hwan's wife.
I had seen the budget report you've made.
It's delivered with such details.
We've worked so hard.
Although.
It isn't that bad for such a new part.
Yes.
So. what about the sound-proof wall construction plan?
Ah. For the populated rural area?
I don't think there's a new contractor for that yet.
We can just have it re-scheduled.
I'll make further adjustment.
This isn't exactly our field of planning.
Our top priority's still the sidewalk sector.
In matters of increasing the aesthetics of the whole area.
Still. we need to minimize the noise of the sidewalk construction.
Excuse me. sir. We've already prepared multi-course dinner for you over there.
Why don't you join us? Let's enjoy it together.
Pardon?
Yes. Together.
Let's go.
How's the food here? Is it delicious?
I think so.
I personally pick this place. sir.
Because you have such a fine taste.
Also. a charismatic face.
Thank you.
Mister Mayor. sir.
I'd like to ask a few questions.
What is it. Mrs. Kim?
You may ask anything.
Why is the sidewalk renovations happened so often?
While it looked like there are still many
other serious things than that.
It's okay if it were only for the damaged parts.
but. why is it that the whole sidewalk have to be repaired?
These days. there are many other districts have nice sidewalk.
So. we must have the same level.
Still.
This project is waste of public's fund. A misuse.
What makes you think that way?
You cared too much of the public interest. aren't you?
Yes. I also cared too much whether if
you're from the Joseon period with that getup.
Joseon period.
Don't say anything anymore.
Let go of me. Let speak my mind.
Then. Mrs. Kim is thinking of
a support for public interest.
I'm not saying this because it's my husband's idea.
The sound-proof wall project for the subway line is a good idea.
Ma'am. policies such as this is not that simple.
Of course. It must've had something to do with you. right?
About the construction project.
Enough. Don't speak any more than this.
Still. The citizen.
they had to be heard from you. too.
As long as we're still The National Republic of Korea.
We still have rights to speak and deliver our opinions.
We had this learned even since elementary schools. right?
It's true. Of course.
But. it must've had a long time for it to be rescheduled. right?
Actually. it'd be within five years.
But. there's a lawyer of the construction company
who took the date forward.
Many citizen had already gave their approvals.
So. it might only happened in about two years.
Is that so? I'll think the sound-proof walls project over first. then.
Pardon? Yes. Of course.
Why are we going out suddenly?
Had you gone crazy?
You should be thankful for it.
I don't expect anything more.
What's with you?
Listen. He's my superior.
How could you offend him?
Really. you...
I do this for your sake. too.
Is it a battle? Are you a fighter?
Isn't that why you had brought me here?
What about our family? What if I lose my job?
So it's like this?
Such hypocrite.
You even had your wife to help.
What?
Can't you be a little more polite?
Calm down.
Aren't you an educated person?
I'd think you would be better than this.
Yet. you're actually easy to be swayed by money.
This woman.
Excuse us.
Let me go.
What a rude w*#$@.
What's with that look? She's the one who started it all
Really.
Watch your mouth.
Are you all right. my husband?
What now?
isn't it too risky like this?
I won't stand still at someone who mocks my wife.
I've run out of patience.
What'd you do if you're fired? Live on the streets?
Well... I might go
collect various paper waste.
Don't worry.
I'd never let you starve.
Anyway. why did you drop out of university?
What's with the sudden question about the past?
Even if I might be fired.
It's not your fault.
My lovely wife gave birth to an angel.
As a parent. I was filled with so much happiness.
I remember. when Ha Neul was born.
She had a pair of pretty eyes and was looked so adorable.
And. I hugged her. wrapped in a soft blanket.
I had to make a choice.
I would protect both you and Ha Neul.
You also know that I raised by my grandmother only. right?
And now's the time to work even harder.
Through every and all troubles ahead.
To create our happiness together.
Such a nice person you are.
I kind of knew why I find you attractive.
Even without the good-looks of a model.
Ah. I think it's not all about money.
Thank you.
Take your cup. too.
Cheers.
Are you asleep yet. Yeon Woo?
What should I do? I can't sleep.
Just sleep. won't you. Howling like a wolf.
His true colours are visible when he's drunk.
Mom.
The time has come.
To cook rice. as a wife would do.
Has the Sun finally rise from the west?
You actually going to cook.
Of course. It's normal for a housewife to cook.
What's wrong with it?
You're weird recently
Anyway. give me some money.
There isn't any.
Don't be that stingy.
It's almost at seven. you'll be late.
It's all right. many of my friends hadn't even wake up at his hour.
You looked different. Do you have a boyfriend?
It's just a friend. A seonbae.
Is that so?
I said. there's nothing.
I'm just an unpopular girl at school.
It's clear as day.
Even with what you just said.
you still mind your appearance.
If only you there's no pimple on your forehead.
it's all good enough.
Stop teasing me. Hurry. give me some money.
You have to tidy up the table over there first.
Then. you can have some money.
Is this a joke?
If you don't help. you won't get any money.
Starting today. its our family motto.
Seriously.
Now you know. I'm your superior. little girl.
Look at these toys.
Some had even already been around since my father's childhood.
This is too expensive.
Have you heard?
The woman who sell these is involved. too.
Really?
I don't understand her either.
Always forcing us to buy the prawn paste.
She might even involved in some kind of corruption.
Unbelievable.
Don't spread such gossip.
What do you mean?
To accuse her without any evidence can be charged.
What are you talking about? Who's getting charged?
Are you all talking about me?
How could we? We'd never do that.
Get off. Stop it.
Have you bought the prawn paste? I'm watching over you all.
Of course. I had bought one.
Eat it well.
Why don't you buy one? Why don't you buy one?
What's with her? She's weird recently.
She might be a spy now.
An agent.
Do you mean. she's a prawn paste seller's agent?
Why do we have to buy it. anyway?
Little boy. are you all right?
Your hand's bleeding.
Corn seller.
When will it be?
Sorry. I'll give it to you after the store's closed.
Give it now. hurry.
How can you run business without any contribution?
Would you prefer if I ask your wife instead?
Ajumma. don't yell at my dad. please.
Ajumma really is a bad person.
This dirty girl. how could you raise a child like this?
Don't scare the children.
Do you know who're you talking to. now?
You'd better close it now. and take your daughter with you.
Mom.
Ha Roo. why are you here? Let's go.
Mom. This ajussi helped me when I fall down.
But. this ajumma told him to leave.
Let's go.
Why are you all gathered here?
Scram!
What is the matter?
This ajussi hasn't pay on time.
Even now. as we meet each other.
He would've pay later.
But. who'd know whether if he would pay or not today.
He might've run off. after he closes his shop.
People do business. they're not thieves.
They won't just run off like that.
Aigoo. your words are scary. This isn't a trial.
A lawsuit is necessary should there be an objection.
Repeaters had been placed over there.
Had you all known that?
What?
I don't even know there are such things on our buildings.
I suppose since communication company
had placed repeaters on the each roof of the buildings.
With the cost of the rent. a few million per year.
if you can well-manage their income.
You'd as successful as a Chinese company in just a few years.
The placement of advertisements. where they shouldn't be.
to sell second-hand clothes and the market business's income.
Had you integrated those incomes
into the building's management costs.
Of course I had. Also...
take them for dinner together.
We've done this often.
It isn't a crime on business misuse. instead...
it's operational misuse crime. according to
the criminal law article 365.
someone else's business property placed under your own name.
is a violation which
has a 10-years sentence at most.
Or. a 30 million fine.
What?
Really.
She droves her to back off.
It's all clear. Do you still unwilling to apologise?
My mistakes. I'm sorry.
Eonnie. you're so cool. But. where did you get all that from?
She's just had it. It's her hidden skill.
Shut up. she'd done her best.
Eonnie.
It was from the children's father.
Right. I heard he was once a Law student in university.
True.
You really have a nice husband.
And handsome. too.
Give me the money. now.
I haven't count it yet.
Just. check it yourself if you don't believe me.
Even if just one is missing.
you're in deep trouble.
Wah. you really are stingy.
Though. not when you bought
all those uber expensive clothes.
Why you.
I'll be back.
What? Do you like doing this now?
Enough. mom...
Come in.
Where's your parent?
They're at work.
Don't you feel hot in that?
It's not.
You looked cute when you're flustered.
Hold on. I think it's too sudden.
Don't you like me?
I still think it's too soon.
Oh. What's that?
Ah. shi...
What a terrible hiding place. We've been busted. Come out.
What are you doing?
Why do you looked so surprised?
This is an interesting game. right?
I'm going home. now.
Why? Where are you going to?
Don't you want to be popular?
It'll be your debut.
B@$#**#!
Come back. you b*#*#!
Today is 10. I'll return in two weeks.
Oh. You've home.
Is something happened?
Turn the light's off. I'd like to sleep.
What happened?
Who did this?
Go out. I don't want to say anything.
Was it your boyfriend who did this?
I don't have any.
If you don't tell me.
I'm afraid I can't help you.
So. I have to tell you the truth?
I don't know what to say.
but. shouldn't you assure me? Comfort me?
To tell me that everything's going to be all right?
Can you..?
It was horrible.
Don't worry. I had to bite him
and escaped.
What do I have to do after this. mom?
Can I to go to school even after all this?
Of course. I'll handle everything.
It's all right. You should go sleep now.
As the Principal of the school.
let's clear things up.
without unnecessary matters.
I'm Kim Jae Hoon's Lawyer.
Although it is a regretful event.
we still have to consider
the consequences on mental scars.
Also. we can come up with the compensation aspects.
Do you and Kim Ha Neul know such matters?
Wait. Please let me have a 5-minute time off.
So. it all come down to this.
Look what had you done.
Seriously. it's all real.
I'm all right. So. I'll just have to agree to their terms.
What's all right?
We would never win against them. anyway.
It's like that.
Our family doesn't have much money.
Let's just stop it and go home.
It doesn't always on money to survive.
Am I right?
Mom.
Let's go.
This much scars and bruises obviously stated that
there was an assault. at least.
As a lawyer.
There'll be many ways around it.
School life is only for a few years.
there'll be a whole new world after that.
But. what if Kim Ha Neul. as a student.
it'll be significantly had an impact on her
if her identity has spread.
Really. It's not like she was raped.
Ha Neul. we're living in The Republic of Korea. right?
We also have the right to sue.
It's just a precaution if you weren't presentable for the trial.
Yes. you have that much money.
But. why don't we take it to a trial?
I have more understandings on aspects of law. actually.
There's an urge to trample on certain someone's future.
Ha Neul's mother.
I don't want it to drags on. either.
But. in such a short time.
I'd like to send him through hell.
Sure. You may run away to another country.
it doesn't matters not where he goes to.
As long as I can put these legs forward.
to let everyone knows that he's guilty. of a rape attempt.
by this ajumma.
While we go through under the law's corridors.
blogs. Twitter. Facebook. all of SNS.
All of social media.
It won't even for a mere year. more than 10 years.
Let people to remember about him.
You wouldn't want that to happen. would you?
Let's go. Ha Neul.
Ha Neul's mother.
From now on. if you'd ever do this again.
I'll report you to the Education Dept.
S*#*! How dare you do this to me!
It's just a little mistake.
Useless. It's not worth it. Such a weak girl is nothing.
What did you say? How dare you to call my daughter's weak.
I'll teach you this.
This would be your first time
to apologise with your head's down.
What a rude brat.
Would we be all right?
Don't worry. They won't dare to touch you.
Also. that lawyer.
Let the terrible man apologise publicly.
It's a mental compensation. too.
To be honest. you're not your usual self. Mom.
It's really weird.
To have you defend me.
Today. you're kind of cool. actually.
Don't just stack the papers.
At it again? Really...
Are these too many?
Don't want to fold those?.
I'll just stack those.
The neck tie's ready.
Thank you.
Have you finished dinner. Ha Neul?
Mom. I've finished 150.
So. I'll get 4.500 from 150.
It's because you also fold these too. thank you dear.
Thank you. thank you very much. I'm going now.
You're welcome.
Yes...
Ha Roo. Have you awake yet. Ha Roo?
Hurry. or we'll be late.
Brush your teeth and wash yourself up clean.
I'll be late. Ah. what a nice smell.
Where's the soup?
Smell's nice.
Here it is.
Let's eat together.
I'll have it with Ha Roo later.
It's the best.
Good morning.
- These fresh bananas are pretty expensive.
- Thank you.
Hurry up. Run. Even if it'd flip your skirt.
Why. you..
I see you've been a lot better now.
My goodness.
You've come.
Have you blend in with the family life yet?
Yes.
You still have a week left.
It might be a little sad for you.
A bit.
Am I going to die?
Hadn't I told you?
Traffic accident.
But. what about the children?
If next week. an accident happened.
to suddenly lost their beloved mother.
Isn't it far too horrible?
Would you like to help and ease the children's life?
Of course. If it's possible. I'll do anything.
Then. use your remaining time to give all of your love in any way you can.
And hope for the best in your remaining time.
I've been seeing you're behaving as if you were a newly-wed couple.
Recently. my life has never been better.
You know what kind of a friend I am. right?
The one who's happy when his friend is. too.
You should've been glad to have a friend like me.
Thank you. Thank you.
I know today is a very special day.
I will always need your help. my friend.
The HR Dept. sent this to me.
It's so sweet. ah.
Chief.
What's the meaning of this?
I shouldn't be placed on the field yet.
It's clearly stated there. right?
It's the Mayor's sign. if you think it's too soon...
Chief.
I was wrong at that time.
Please. give me another chance.
Sorry.
You had taught your wife well.
Women with low education isn't always nosy. apparently.
You'll hit me again?
I'd forget all the mockeries about my wife.
I can tolerate it. this time.
Isn't our anniversary still quite long ahead?
Or. do you miss to date me?
Sung Hwan-ssi. if I might suddenly...
Soo Yeon...
I'm going to be transferred into field work.
Therefore. I have to be there next month.
- So...
- Is it because.
We had it against Chief Choi?
I'd do my best and return as fast as I can.
It's all because of me. I'm so sorry.
Never mind. it's not your fault.
It's all right.
Ah. too sweet.
Thank you for your time. to meet me.
The person herself who caused the troubles come to me.
I don't even ask for it.
How could this come back at us. things that had you upset.
I would even down on my knees if you'd asked me to.
Please. give us another chance this time.
Am I a gangster? Who'd demand you to kneel down.
I don't have much time.
Life is never easy. ma'am.
How could we ever solve this?
Society had became so insensitive recently.
You should know that. ajumma.
Wait. please sit down for a minute.
I still have an official work to do.
I know. Just. have a seat for awhile.
Hello. is this the construction's secretary. Kim Ho Jung?
I've just appointed to re-take on the construction's case.
By Lawyer Lee Yi Ahn.
I'd just want to ask something.
Because it is a case on the rework of the construction plan.
I wonder if there's
a civil servant being involved?
Is it Section Chief Choi? Bribery. perhaps?
All right. I understand.
Who are you. really?
Me? I'm just a wife of Kim Sung Hwan.
Don't just look at it. Hurry. which one is it?
I can't. I have to buy menopouse medicine for my mom.
What? Menopause. you said?
Mom is feeling a bit unwell because of menopause.
But. she's doing well now.
Is that so?
See you later.
Oh my..
Little boy. are you all right?
A young boy named Ha Roo.
6 years old.
Are you his guardian?
Mom. I'm his mother.
He has Retinitis Pigmentosa.
( Retinitis Pigmentosa is an inherited. degenerative eye disease that causes severe vision impairment.
)
It has retinal degenerative symptoms. such as decreased vision.
That's why. he's likely to stumble over.
What? Retinitis Pigmentosa?
It looked like it might had been quite long for him.
He'd been in pain.
Could it be treated?
Surgery would be a way.
but. there might still be
Eventual blindness.
How can a child of our family
possibly had to suffer with something like this?
Genetic inheritance holds a high factor.
You inherited it.
Because. your mother had it too. right?
One of her eyes is blind. isn't it?
Although. several surgeries after that
were enabled her retina to be treated.
Those surgeries ultimately had
taken serious impact upon her family.
They didn't know that
her mother had been in pain.
She didn't want to make her family
to be worried over her.
Think about it.
How could things like these ever happened?
Why are there so many issues.
You've overthinking everything.
I'll lose the time to be a mother.
I can never able to pretend as a mother anymore.
How could I inherited a sick body?
Because. you're Ha Roo's mother now.
How could this ever happened to Ha Roo's mother?
This woman have too many problems.
It's three weeks before her death.
- Lee Yi Ahn.
- This life...
It's like she has too much sins...
Even sins are able to be erased off.
while it might be hard.
How could even just for a child's disease.
it's unable to be cured?
Is this what you call the law of the universe?
Oh. you're here.
Don't think about it too much.
Don't be a weak mother for him.
I'm positive Ha Roo's going to be cured.
Take the medicine regularly. all right?
Look out for his injuries.
all right. Yes. thank you.
Ha Roo. your family is really strong.
I don't even remember my father's face.
I don't ever wanted to be taken
back by my father and mother anymore.
So. I had burnt their photos and clothes.
I hate my father.
Who went and left my mother and I.
I was really ruthless back then.
For I can be independent of anyone.
Even when I was successful.
I don't know.
There will always be someone
we can rely to when we're in troubles.
Loved ones are the real meaning of our life.
This car would take you back.
Not now. I still can't leave Ha Roo.
Forget it. There's not much time left.
I can't leave the children suffer the pain.
I only wish to see him awake.
I'm warning you. Don't be too involved
with her own personal life.
This is because of me. Please.
It all started from the accident.
By going with this car. would not solve everything.
I wish Ha Neul and Ha Roo to be able
to live in the house.
Then. you wanted to stay here and become their mother?
You'd give up your life for them?
If it's possible. I'd do it.
I'd give up my life as a lawyer.
- I beg of you.
- Lee Yi Ahn.
Do you want to get into trouble?
Do you know what I'm saying?
Just go while you can.
Hurry up. Get on.
What are you doing?
Let me choose my own life.
Please.
Please help me.
I can't let you act like this.
Please. Please.
Just this once.
It was so close.
There is not much time left.
Go.
Mom.
You've come.
It's time for Ha Roo.
I'll wait for him while he's in the surgery room.
Mom. I'm going to school. now.
Hold on. Ha Neul.
You'd be a successful actress. Ha Neul.
I believe in you.
Why are you suddenly say that?
I just wish to see my daughter to be happy.
I know. but this is too much.
I'm going first. so you don't have to be worried.
I'll return to the hospital after school. okay?
Bye bye.
Mom.
I don't want to see you suffer. my son.
Even if you can't see my face.
You still can hear my voice. right?
Yes. your voice's clear. mom.
If I were to suddenly go somewhere very far away.
Ha Roo still has to be strong through everything.
I'm going to be a good boy
and will still wait for your return. mom.
But. you have to return soon.
Are you crying?
I'm not.
My son. Ha Roo.
Don't ever forget to love me.
Of course. I really love you. mom.
Why hadn't you eaten yet?
Hurry up. and eat. I'll stay here.
Go.
You may call me Ha Neul's mother from now on.
It's all right.
Ah. Why are you keep changing like this.
I coudn't before. yet now I can?
All right. Ha Neul's mother.
I'm so sorry if I have to leave you to somewhere far.
What do you mean somewhere far?
To be honest. I still want to be with you and the children.
You'll leave to eat. right?
All right. Hurry. you should go.
Doctor. The patient's conscious. suddenly.
Have you fully awake. ma'am?
Who are you?
- Is this Ha Neul's house?
- No.
Kim Sung Hwan.Ha Neul and Ha Roo lived here. right?
No. there's no such person.
Be careful.
Mom. Mom. Mom.
I found evidence of illegal doings
on the construction's plan.
Everything's against Chairman Park is there. too.
Why do you give me this?
I'd think you're the one suited for the exposure.
Seonbae's deserved this.
To reveal the truth would looked cool and fit on you.
Why's this sudden change.
It's not as the usual Lee Yi Ahn.
I recently just had a very beautiful dream.
A dream. Do you mean...
Why are you suddenly have to move?
My loneliness makes me
feel so sad.
Why are you taking that every day?
Nothing in particular.
It looked so old.
It's my mom's.
There must be a lot of memories inside.
I'd go to the next room. all right?
Father.
My daughter's more precious than my own life.
I love you.
Father.
Do you see me now?
I really miss you. dad.
You looked so handsome.
Mom. I had just know that you love me.
Thank you for raising your daughter.
I'll be seeing you back sometimes. okay?
I had been too busy. I'd just want to rest my mind.
Why is it have to go as far as New Zealand?
Rest well.
Don't cause troubles there.
I'm inside the place already. I'll hung up the phone.
Excuse me.
5G. ajumma is sitting next to me.
Ha Roo.
How do you know my name?
How could you be here?
Can you see these words?
Of course. I know alphabet already.
Why is.. this little boy.
My son had run off. I'm sorry.
Get in.
Anyway. why is it only you and the children
who go to The New Zealand?
Because mom... Mom had went to heaven.
Hey. you...
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I have a friend there. And we're allowed to stay there temporarily.
Is that so?
What about you?
I'm going to see my father.
Oh.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm